《实习医生格蕾》前情提要
Previously  on "Grey's Anatomy"...
我通过了
I passed?
你不再是实习生了
You're not an intern anymore.
乔治的眼里根本没有我
George doesn't know I exist.
你想跟我约会吗
Do you want to go on a date with me?
万一我不喜欢这样呢
What if I'm not into it?
我不会让你这样对我的  阿历克斯
I'm not letting you do this to me, Alex.
我知道自己是个混蛋
I know I'm being an ass.
我想我找到了一个治疗的方法了
I think I found a way to save lives.
我可以找病人来进行临床试验
I could find patients for a clinical trial.
肿瘤变小了  病毒起效了
The tumor's shrinking. the virus is working.
-你还写日记  -不是我的
- You keep a diary?  - It's not mine.
-那是谁的  -你母亲的
- Whose is it?  - Your mother's.
我是顽石
I am a rock.
我是孤岛
I am an island.
这两句话几乎适用于
That's the mantra of pretty much
我认识的每一个医生
every surgeon I've ever met.
我们自认为很独立  不合群  特立独行
We like to think we're independent, loners, mavericks...
认为自己的工作
that all we need to do our jobs
只需要一间手术室
is an O.R., a scalpel and a willing body.
一把手术刀  以及一个病人
a scalpel and a willing body.
杨今晚值班是吗
Is Yang on call tonight?
是的  否则这里怎么会这么干净
Uh, yeah. Why do you think it's so clean in here?
但事实上  就连我们当中的
But the truth is, not even
最棒的人都不可能独自完成
the best of us can do it alone.
手术就像生活  需要团队合作
Surgery, like life, is a team sport.
我想说  慢慢来  这个想法
Can I just say, the whole "taking it slow" thing?
太棒了
Best idea ever.
这样的确能减轻压力
It really takes the pressure off.
没错
Mm. Yeah.
我们可以  单纯的约会
We can just, you know, hang out
刨去那些  过高的期望
without all the... the expectations.
-干嘛那么急  -没错
-Why rush things?  - Exactly.
最终  我们都必须正视生活并做出选择
And eventually, you've got to get off the bench and decide...
我究竟与谁并肩作战
What team are you batting for?
要知道  同居的乐趣之一就是能共进早餐
You know,one of the joys of cohabitation is having breakfast together.
今天不行  因为贝利叫我们早点去
Well, I can't today because Bailey paged us in early.
我想你还没看过
I guess you don't have time to look
我们发表在医学杂志上的那篇文章
at our work in a major medical journal.
我们的临床试验发表了
They published our clinical trial? mm-hmm.
还上了封面
It's on the cover.
非手术治疗恶性神经胶质瘤的新方法
"a new method in treating inoperable malignant gliomas...
谢博德氏法
the Shepherd method."
你觉得怎么样
What do you think?
-这是你的照片  很大的照片  -你表情不对
- It's a picture, a big picture of you. - You're making a face.
我没有  我很喜欢这张照片
I'm not making a face. I love that picture.
我得走了
I have to go.
谢博德氏法
"the Shepherd method".
是时候给医院来点正面宣传了
It's about time this hospital got some good publicity for a change.
我听说你找到捐赠者了
Oh, I heard you found a donor.
是的  万事俱备只欠东风
Yes, sir. The last piece of the puzzle finally fell into place.
就是今天  贝利医生
This is the day, Dr. Bailey
西雅图圣恩医院重振的时刻到了
the day that Seattle Grace comes back swinging.
谢博德上了国家期刊的封面
Shepherd on the front page of a national journal,
大谈创新手术的理论
Bragging rights to a flashy surgery
我看西部恩典医院还做不到吧
I don't see Mercy West taking on a project of this magnitude, do you?
还是等那件事完美结束了再庆祝吧
I'd rather wait to celebrate till we pull this thing off.
对  不要影响到那件事
Yeah, that's a good call. we don't want to jinx it.
西部恩典医院  小样
Eat that, Mercy West.
天哪  我到处在找你
God, I've been looking everywhere for you.
我一早做了个腭成形术
Well, I had an early morning palatoplasty.
你看了吗  谢博德氏法
You see this? "the Shepherd method"?
是的  很轰动
Yeah, yeah, very impressive.
-昨晚  爱瑞...  -你觉得他们PS过他的照片吗
- Listen, last night, Erica... - You think they airbrushed his picture?
他脸上居然连毛孔都看不见
I mean, the man does not have one damn pore.
你能不能专心点  我现在需要你
Could you focus? I need you right now.
好吧  虽然我现在有些累
All right, well, I'm a little exhausted,
但如果你想跳上来快活一下的话...
but if you want to hop on and do all the work...
不  我要你听我说
No, I need to talk.
昨晚  我和爱瑞  我们...
Last night, Erica and I... we...
我们那个了
We did it. sort of.
恭喜你了
Congratulations.
不
No. no, no.
一点都不好
It was not good at all.
我卡住了
I choked.
我没法继续
I couldn't go down there.
我尽力了  可就是觉得太怪了
I-I tried, but it just felt so weird
就像是换我做妇科手术那样
and clinical, like gynie rotation.
早上我趁她没醒就溜了
I left this morning before she got up.
我没法面对她
I couldn't even face her.
要是我跟爱瑞
What if... what if me and Erica are...
我跟她在一起  是错误的  那怎么办
what if... what if we were a mistake?
-你去哪儿  -我不想谈这事
- Where are you going?  - I can't talk about this.
别装了  你巴不得我跟你讲这事
Oh, come on. You love talking about this stuff.
女同题材  多么刺激
Girl on girl. It's hot.
俩女人在一起缠绵  是很刺激
Two girls getting nasty and loving it? That's hot.
听一个女人抱怨她的遭遇有多糟
One girl talking about how much it sucked?
没意思  不想听
Depressing and wrong.
我不想听
Just wrong.
主任让我们每人挑个实习生给乔治
The chief wants us to give George one of our interns?
除了格蕾  她已经缺了欧麦利
Except for Grey. She already lost O'malley.
-你就扔个最差的出来  -拜托  他们都很差
- Just dump your dead weight. - Oh, please. they're all dead weight.
所以我需要四个而不是三个
That's why I need all four of them, not three.
乔治正在办手续  领白大褂
George is filling out paperwork, getting his real live doctor wings,
所以我觉得该是时候装饰一下他的柜子了
So I thought now would be a good time to decorate his locker.
咖啡给我
Give me that coffee.
我没想要署名  可临床试验是我的主意
Okay. I don't even want the credit, but the clinical trial was my idea.
我还得不仅一次求他做这试验
And I had to beg him to do it, more than once.
你想要署名很正常  我是你我就会要的
It's okay you want the credit. I would want the credit.
别打主治医生的主意  遭殃的会是你自己
When you screw the attendings, you get screwed.
-他们权利很大  -你可以搞实习生
- They have all the power. - Interns. You could screw interns.
我是说约会  住院医生可以约会实习生
I mean date. Residents could date interns,
因为我们不具威胁
'cause we're nonthreatening.
我看过一个调查
I read this study once that said that
实习生很少有投诉性骚扰的
Interns hardly ever file sexual harassment
原因是我们觉得在医院里是弱势群体
Claims because we feel so weak and powerless in the hospital environment,
实习生  又一块肥肉
Interns... the other white meat.
-我们去哪  -到了就知道了
- Where are we going?  - You'll see when we get there.
贝利医生  我今天是跟着斯隆医生的
Dr. Bailey, I'm actually on Dr. Sloan's service today.
所有人都放下手头的活  都跟着我走
Everyone's off their services. You're all with me.
我们这是去哪
Where are we going?
到了就知道了
You'll see when we get there.
你看到你的柜子了没
Hey, did you see your locker?
我在里面放了香烛
I put a smelly candle in it,
-你的衣服会有股玉桂卷的香味  -多谢
- So now your scrubs are gonna smell like cinnamon bun. - Gosh, thanks.
贝利医生  斯隆医生正在做经腭徙前术
Dr. Bailey, Dr. Sloan is doing a transpalatal advancement.
这可是我第一次见识的机会
I've never seen one.
汉娜说我可以参加她的主动脉穿刺手术
Hahn said I could scrub in on her aortic bypass.
我真的得回门诊部
And I really need to get to the clinic.
我安排了护士在那
I've staffed it with nurses and p.s.,
但我是唯一的值班医生了
but I'm the only doctor on call,
-还要做行政工作  -今天你们的事都搁一边
- And I've got administrative work to... - Today is not about you.
不管今天你们跟着哪个医生
It is not about whose services you wish to be on.
你们的前程都放一边  今天听我的
It's not about your career. This is about me.
我有个手术准备了很久
This is a project I've been working on for a long time,
对我很重要  所以对你们也很重要
And it's very important to me, therefore it will be very important to you.
唯一顺利完成这事儿的方法就是
And the only way we can pull this thing off
我们必须团队合作
is if we work together as a team,
所以今天你们不是15个医生
So today, you are not 15 individual doctors,
你们是一队医生  代表我们医院
You are one team of surgeons representing this hospital.
每个人听清楚了
Is everybody clear on that?
-什么手术会需要那么多医生  -我不知道
- Um, why would they need so many doctors for one surgery? - I don't know.
因为不止一个手术
Because it's not just one surgery.
有12个手术  6对肾移植手术
It's 12 surgeries... 6 kidney transplants in six O.R.s,
要同时进行
all at the same time.
肾脏配对移植
Paired matching kidney donation.
6个人将肾脏捐献给6个陌生人
A 6-way swap... 6 people donate kidneys to total strangers,
6个人从6个陌生人那获得肾脏
Six people get kidneys from total strangers.
12个人将会高兴得离开医院
12 people walk away happy.
肾脏配对移植
Paired matching kidney donation.
又称多米诺手术
Otherwise known as... dude, a domino surgery.
斯坦·莫休  46岁  高血压引起肾衰竭
Stan Mercer, 46, chronic renal failure secondary to high blood pressure.
他妻子想要捐肾给他  可惜不匹配
His wife here wanted to donate a kidney to him,but she wasn't a match.
所以她将捐肾给那里的陈女士
So she will be donating her kidney to Ms.Chen over there,
她们的肾脏相匹配
who is a match,
莫休先生则会接受这位小伙子的捐赠
while Mr.Mercer will be getting a kidney from this young man today.
很高兴见到你
Nice to meet you.
P.J.  拜托
P.J., please.
肯特·瓦林  58岁  糖尿病引起肾衰竭
Kurt Walling 58 chronic renal failure secondary to diabetes.
他儿子P.J.与他不匹配  所以瓦林先生将
His son P.J. wasn't a match, so Mr.Walling will be
接受赫曼女士的捐赠
getting Ms.Herman's kidney today.
-谢谢你  赫曼女士  -叫我林赛就行
- Thanks for the kidney Ms.Herman. - Call me Lindsay.
我们今天会离得很近
We're gonna be pretty close by the end of the day.
其他病人都类似
And so on and so forth.
为什么你们看上去呆头呆脑的
Why do you still look stupid?
也许我们该做一份名单
Well, maybe if we had a cheat sheet.
赫曼女士捐给瓦林先生
Ms.Herman gives her kidney to Mr.Walling.
瓦林先生的儿子捐给莫休先生
Mr.Walling's son gives his kidney to Mr.Mercer.
莫休先生的妻子捐给陈女士
Mr.Mercer's wife gives her kidney to Ms.Chen.
陈女士的妹妹捐给帕特先生
Ms.Chen's sister gives her kidney to Mr. Patel.
帕特先生的妻子捐给罗宁女士
Mr. Patel's wife gives her kidney to Ms.Loring,
她和她表姐 郭美斯女士一起来的
who came in with her cousin, Ms.Gomez,
她表姐将捐肾给职业笛手卡拉斯先生
who's giving her kidney to Mr. Cross, the professional flautist.
其他没有过目不忘本领的人
For those of you without a photographic memory,
去会议室里的墙上看
It's up on a board in the conference room.
为什么我们非得同时做6个手术
And why do we have to do all six transplants at one time?
保证没有人会在紧要关头退出
So no one backs out at the last minute.
为什么退出  能参加这手术简直是梦寐以求
Why would anybody back out? It's such an incredible thing to be a part of.
器官传递过程很恐怖  我要退出
Well, passing the organ's kinda creepy. I'd back out.
所以整个手术就像一套多米诺骨牌
Yeah, yeah, that's why this whole surgery is a giant house of cards.
少了一个捐献者  就都完了
If we lose one donor, we lose them all.
所以你们除了全力手术之外
So you will not only provide excellent medical care,
还要尽力让病人保持愉悦
but you will keep your patients happy.
我们必须保证病人们
We need to make sure this whole thing
在手术前都好好的  还有什么问题
doesn't fall apart before the surgery. Any questions?
我听说过波士顿简恩医院做的多米诺手术
Um, I heard when they did a domino at Boston Gen,
每个住院医生都可以
The residents all got to keep one of
在瓶子里保留一个坏肾作为纪念
the dead kidneys in a jar as a souvenir.
我也要一个肾
I want a kidney in a jar.
-我也要  -如果他们都有  那我也要
- Me, too, can I have a kidney?  - Well, if they get kidneys, I get a kidney.
数量有限  我先要的  我...
Quantities are limited. I asked first. Can we?
谁都别想带个肾回去
No one is taking home a kidney in a jar.
坏肾不是你们咖啡桌上的装饰
Diseased kidneys are not tchotchkes for your coffee table.
全都给我去工作
Now go. go.
你还好吗
Hey, you okay?
贝利把所有外科的住院医生和实习生都带走了
Uh, Bailey snagged all the surgical residents and interns,
我就只能用精神科实习生  一点儿都不机灵
So I'm stuck with the psych interns. Not the sharpest.
好吧  既然你很忙  我就长话短说
Okay, you're busy. I'll be brief.
如果今晚你不值班的话  我们可以...
I was thinking,if you weren't on call tonight,that,maybe we could
去我那儿  叫外卖  一起看电影
uh, go to my place, order in dinner, rent a movie.
今晚  你今晚还要?
Tonight? You want to get together again tonight?
-昨晚我很快活  -快活
- Well, I had a lot of fun last night. - Fun.
决定好了告诉我
Anyway, just let me know.
如你们所知  你们中有一个要去跟着欧麦利
Okay, as you may know, one of you is going to O'malley today.
我去  我愿意去
Oh, me! I-I'll go if you need a volunteer.
我得先确定你们谁最蠢  再决定让谁去
I decide who gets to go after I decide which one of you sucks the most.
你最好别给我装蠢  我能看得出来
And you better not suck on purpose, because I will know.
亲爱的 你想要看看书或听听音乐吗
Honey, would you like your book or some music,
做些能让你放松的事情
Something to help you relax?
我不知道  也许喝点水好一点
I don't know. maybe some water.
冰水怎么样
How about some ice chips instead?
你的脚踝有点肿
Your ankles are looking a little thick.
我妻子喜欢关注我的液体潴留情况
My wife loves tracking my fluid retention.
麦根
And, megan,
你能过来这边吗
Will you please come over here and
绑住针头  我们就可以开始透析了
Tape the needles so we can start dialysis?
说得像个真医生一样
Sounds just like a real doctor.
在受赠者名单上面
Uh, it says here that you don't have
没有你伴侣的名字 赫曼女士
a loved one in the domino, ms.herman
没有
no.
你将无偿把肾捐赠给一个
So you're just donating a kidney to
完全不认识的陌生人
a complete stranger for nothing in return?
没什么了不起的
it's really no big deal.
我有两个肾  他们说一个肾就可以活下去了  所以
I have two kidneys, and they say you can live with one, so...
你开玩笑吧  你做的事情太伟大了
Are you kidding? that's amazing, what you're doing.
器官共享联合网络里总是器官短缺
U.n.o.s. is always short on organs.
如果全世界的人都这么做
If everyone in the world did this-- yeah,
那将会世界和平  人人拥有爱与纯真嘛
It'd be all peace and love and unicorns.
她懂了 格蕾
She gets it, grey.
别人总是 你强!  烦死我了
I'm so sick of all the "yay, you."
我完全明白
I totally understand.
主任整天都让我接受记者采访
Oh. the chief has got me doing press all day with journalists.
我的脸开始笑到痛了
My face is starting to hurt from smiling.
我已经按了
Uh-huh. I already pushed that.
我按就会快一点来
it comes faster when I push it.
-那肯定是谢博德氏方法  -真有趣
-Oh, must be that shepherd method. -funny.
我想走楼梯
I think I'll take the stairs.
梅瑞狄斯 你因为这个觉得烦恼吗
Meredith, are you bothered by this?
我为什么会觉得烦恼呢
why would I be bothered?
你不能把那叫做谢博德格蕾方法
You can't call it the shepherd-grey method
因为这样人们会觉得你只是个助手
Because then people would think you had help.
我真的要把我的肾捐给那个老头吗
So do I really have to give my kidney to that old guy?
-莫休先生 绝对没过50岁  -我的儿子才22
-Mr. mercer couldn't be more than 50. -my son's 22.
对他来说  超过40的人就在死亡边缘了
To him, everyone over 40 is on the brink of death.
-八月时已经23岁了  -对
-Turned 23 in august.  -oh, that's right.
也许我们可以
Maybe we could have
在医院举办一个延迟派对
a little belated party here in the hospital,
给你买个冰淇淋蛋糕
Get you an ice cream cake.
-你以前很喜欢的  -我七岁的时候喜欢
-You used to love those. -yeah, when I was 7.
听好  我来这里不是跟你团圆的
Look, I'm not here for a reunion.
我只想快点完成然后离开这里  听到了吗
I just want to get this over with and get out of here, okay?
那你现在是每周做四次透析吗
So you are on dialysis four times a week now?
这时他们也应该带我去做透析了
They might as well chain me to the machine at this point.
我的肾坏了  我借着时间活着
My kidneys are shot. I'm living on borrowed time.
所以有这么个儿子能为我捐肾  我很幸运
So I'm pretty lucky to have a son who would do this for me.
你有钱可以换肾  这才叫幸运
You're lucky you're loaded.
究竟我什么时候能拿到那一万块
So when do I get the 10,000 bucks
手术前还是手术后
before or after the surgery?
圣诞节礼物
It's a christmas gift.
现在才十月份
Well, it's october.
我看到你们俩在外徘徊着
I see you two hovering.
假设说  一个病人
Hypothetically, say a patient was...
为了一个肾  付儿子钱  会发生什么事情呢
Paying his son for a kidney, what exactly would happen?
买肾
Paying money for a kidney?
假如
Hypothetically.
就像不久前
like someone stole an organ herself
某人偷了一个器官
not that long ago,
你应该知道
You should know,
会发生的事情就是
What would happen is
你的病人不能参加交换计划
your patient would be out of the exchange.
也就是说  这个人
Which means that this person,
由于她的丈夫不能再得到一个肾
Since her husband's no longer getting a kidney,
会退出
would drop out.
然后他们会退出  他们也会退出
Then they would drop out, then they would drop out,
整个计划将泡汤
Then the whole thing would fall apart.
这就是会发生的事
That's what would happen.
如果你们所说的
So if you both are suggesting that
就是现在发生的事情
that's what's going on here,
你们得十分确认这是真的
You'd better be damn sure about it.
只是一份礼物
It's just a gift.
提早把礼物塞到圣诞袜而已
Uh, an early stocking stuffer.
大多数你这个年龄的女生  就只知道逛街
Most girls your age, they're busy shopping.
而你在医院把肾捐给一个陌生人
You're in the hospital giving a kidney to a stranger.
我并不是你口中的圣人
Oh, I'm not such a saint.
也许我丈夫用的不是你的肾
Your kidney may not be going directly to my husband,
但是你是他今天的救命恩人之人
But you're one of the people saving his life today.
在我看来  你就像特蕾莎修女(因慈善获得诺贝尔和平奖)
To me, your mother teresa.
亲爱的  你能不能
Honey, would you mind
给我拿一条湿毛巾呢
running and getting a wet washcloth for me?
我只是  行  当然可以  失陪一下
I'm just-- oh, yeah, of course. excuse me.
谢谢
Thank you.
你知道
You know
我妈妈独自发明格蕾氏法
my mother invented the grey method all by herself.
你知道吗  也许你不该再看她的日记了
You know, maybe you should stop reading her diary.
这会让你觉得自己不够分量
It's gonna make you feel inadequate.
她已经死了  她属于过去  可是仍然超越我
She's dead and in the past and still outpacing me.
好  看看  那边那个实习生  他干净不
Okay, see, see that intern over there? is he clean?
什么
Huh? what?
我刚在想
Well, I was just thinking
莱西说的话  你知道的
what lexopedia said, and, you know,
她可能知道其中的重要性
She may be on to something.
你要跟实习生睡吗
you're gonna sleep with an intern?
只是抓抓痒
It'd just be scratching the itch.
已经很久没那个了
It's been a long time.
我不能这样下去了
I can't do this.
这些人都说我有多
All these people telling me how
伟大  无私  奉献  我  我只是
Wonderful and selfless and giving I am-- i-i
我再也受不了啦  特别是她
Can't take it anymore, especially not from her.
行  降低你的声音
All right, just keep your voice down.
你看到她的脸吗  感谢我救你一命
Did you see her face, thanking me for saving your life?
斯坦  这太疯狂啦
Stan, this is crazy.
你答应过我你会跟她讲的  求求你
You promised you would tell her. please!
莫休先生  有什么事吗
Ah. mr. mercer, is everything okay?
-有事  事实上  我不太舒服  -告诉她
-No, I don't feel so good, actually. -tell her!
如果过去三年对你是有意义的
If the past three years have meant anything to you
你就得告诉她
you have to tell her!
斯坦
Stan?
我并不是白痴  我知道你外面有个女人
I'm not an idiot. I know there have been other women.
这些年来  我告诉自己  你们只有性没有爱  只有性
All these years, I told myself it was just sex. it's just...
天啊  斯坦  她为了你捐肾
My god, stan. she's giving a kidney for you.
这不是有性无爱  这是家庭观念
That--that's not sex. it's family.
他那个  心脏酶素和心电图都很正常
All right, his cardiac enzymes and e.k.g. look good.
他会急性焦虑发作  腾出手术室  让他做手术
He had an acute anxiety attack. I can clear him for surgery.
我为你什么事都愿意做
I do everything for you.
我放弃了整个人生  就为了让你做透析
I've given up my entire life to get you to dialysis,
开车送你去医院
Drive you to the doctors
我没有要求你为我做任何事
I didn't ask you to do any of that.
我自己会开车  我会自己倒果汁
I can drive a car. I can pour my own juice.
我病倒了  不是变老了
I got sick, not elderly.
不用担心
Well, don't worry.
我不会再为你做任何事情
I won't do one more thing for you,
也就代表我不会捐肾
and that includes giving a kidney.
打电话给器官共享联合网络
Get on the phone with u.n.o.s.
告诉他们我们需要一个肾
Tell them we need a kidney
能够与莫休夫人的抗体相配的
that matches mrs. mercer's antibodies.
在器官共享联合网络找器官  希望渺茫
U.n.o.s. is a long shot.
这是我们唯一的希望  现在去
It's the only shot we have. now go, now.
她不过只个才第二年住院医生
She's barely a second-year resident.
我制造了病毒  她协助而已
I made the virus. she assisted.
迈克·乔丹投篮时  没人在意助攻的是谁
When michael jordan scores, no one cares about the assist.
-我不知道  芝加哥公牛队  -你懂我意思吗
-I don't know. scottie pippen... -you know what I mean.
这些女人  她们每件事都想太多了
These women, they overthink everything.
有人今天脾气不好  什么事
Somebody's cranky today. what is that?
腭裂的试验性治疗
"experimental treatments for cleft palates."
你在自己搞医学试验  是不是
Huh. you're working on your own clinical trial, aren't you?
我  我只是  我在做一些研究而已
I'm--i'm just-- I'm doing a little research.
看到我就让你想到自己
The very sight of me reminds you that you've not made
没有对医学历史作出贡献  是不是
One worthwhile contribution to medical history, doesn't it?
-出去  -你该读读我的文章
-Get out. -you should read my article.
会充实你的人生  使你变得更完美
It will enrich your life, make you a better man.
我留着上厕所的时候看
I'm saving it for the bathroom.
是从办公室开始的  你知道  灯光  玩耍
It started as an office thing, you know, light, fun.
然而一天你起来
And then one day you wake up, and...
你满脑子想的都是这个比自己大的人
This older guy is all you can think about.
你愿意为他做任何事情  甚至捐肾
You'd do anything for him, even give a kidney.
为什么
Why?
我也可以救他的命啊
I could save his life, too.
我的意思是  她是嫁给了他  但是今天我救他的命
I mean,she may be married to him but I'm saving his life today,too.
那最终他就得作出选择
So then he'll finally have to choose.
选她还是我
Her or me?
很明显  爱瑞喜欢  这不算性交的性交
Apparently, erica loved it, the non-sex sex.
-我猜她想继续  -那些女人总是要求我再来
-I think she might want more.-happens to me all the time with women.
我差点忘了  她们都傻傻的
I barely remember it, their minds are blown.
这就是你的圣言啊
that's your sage advice?
我是个世界一流的外科医生
I'm a world-class surgeon,
不仅整形外科而且耳鼻喉科
double boarded in plastics and e.n.t.
我有更有意义的事情要做
I have more meaningful and worthwhile things
-而不是给予做爱意见  -例如呢
-To do than dispense sex advice.  -yeah, like what?
-说得好  -不要这样  马克  我需要你帮忙
-Nice.  -oh, come on. no, mark, I need your help.
借过一下
Excuse me.
在干什么
What is going on?
-在决定要把哪些实习生给乔治  -在我们面前
-Trying to decide which of our interns to give to george. -in front of us.
他们在我们面前决定  就像博览会的牲畜一样
They're deciding in front of us, like livestock at a state fair.
我觉得我想要莱西  她记性好
I think I'll keep lexopedia. she remembers many things.
她会洗澡  这就省了很多我想说的话
Mm-hmm. and she bathes, which is much more than I can say for...
那边那个臭臭二号
Stinky two over there.
-你发臭的  -格拉西艾拉填表填得太垃圾了
-You smell. -well, graciella charts like crap.
但她会接线
But she can put in a line.
另外  克莱尔  差点用跟尿液管阉了一个人
Claire,on the other hand, nearly castrated a guy with a catheter.
-我们能听到你说话  -我不想要皮尔斯了
-We can hear you.  -I might dump Pierce.
-他失败在哪方面  -我只是不想叫他的名字
-Ooh, how does he suck?  -I just hate saying the name pierce.
我们应该反抗
Mm. we should revolt.
他们会更尊重我们的
They'd respect us more
如果我们不是这么谦卑的话
if we didn't participate in our own humiliation.
对
Yeah.
你先反抗  我跟着你
You revolt first, and I'll follow.
器官公享联合网络那边有消息吗
Hey, have you heard from u.n.o.s. yet?
仍在找配对器官
still searching for a match.
-目前还没有  -我希望他们能熬过来
-But so far, nothing.  -I hope they come through.
我的病人真的需要一个肾
My guy really needs a kidney.
伊泽贝尔  他们全部都需要肾
Yeah, they all need kidneys, izzie.
如果德里克需要一个肾  我不会给他的
If derek needed a kidney, I wouldn't give him one.
他会把荣誉抢走
He'd take the credit.
他会说那个肾是神奇般地自己长出来的
He'd say he magically grew it himself.
我的病人病了15年了
My guy's been sick for 15 years.
你能想象你得这样生活吗
Can you imagine having your life on hold like that?
而且  他的儿子这么讨厌
Plus, he's got such a crappy kid.
你  我有说过能放下盘子吗
Hey! did I say you could put that down?
没有对吧  那拿起来啊
No，so pick it up.
-软弱  没有耐力  -对  但他听话啊
-Weak. no stamina.  -yeah, but he takes orders.
这是事实
True. true.
我丈夫究竟能不能得到一个肾
Is my husband getting a kidney or not?
稍等  我妹妹呢
wait, what about my sister?
如果她今天换不了肾
If she's not getting a kidney today,
我不会把我的肾捐给陌生人的
I am not giving mine to some stranger.
我会尽力让每个人在今天都能换肾
I will do my best to make sure everyone gets a kidney today.
一有消息  我会马上通知大家  麻烦出去
I'll update you as soon as I have information. please.
主任  我  我已经控制住了状况
Sir, i--i've got this under control.
我让格蕾联系器官共享联合网络
I have grey talking with u.n.o.s.
-我还让  -我们是国内新闻的特别报道
-I have  -we are being featured on the national news.
所有人的注意力都集中在西雅图圣恩
All eyes are on seattle grace.
解决它
Fix this.
是的  主任
Yes, sir.
我被刺又被戳  像只实验兔一样
I have been poked and prodded like a lab rat,
居然什么也做不了
what, all for nothing?
我们需要花些时间共聚
We got to spend time with each other.
这很重要
That's not nothing.
现在你想起要和我一起生活了
Oh, oh, now you want to spend time together?
你已经迟到了20年
Well, you're about 20 years too late.
所以  我什么都没得到
So, yeah, nothing.
-P.j...  -如果不做手术了我还能拿到1万块吗
-P.j... -do I still get the $10,000 if the surgery doesn't happen?
如果不能  我就要走了  我还有自己的生活
'cause if not, I'm outta here. I have a life to get back to.
求你了  我需要你
Please. I need you.
只要你能  再耐心点
If you could... just be patient a little bit longer...
我差点揍那孩子一顿
I was gonna punch that kid.
我是想说  这个自私的白痴  他爸爸病了
I mean, what kind of a selfish idiot-- his father is sick,
他病的那么严重  他却只想只他那点破钱
He's really sick, and all he cares about is his stupid money.
好吧  他一定做过什么才让这孩子这么恨他
All right,the guy must have done something really bad to make the kid so angry.
也许他只是关心自己的儿子
maybe he just cares about his son,
而那个笨蛋却闹情绪拒绝他的关心
but the moron is too emotionally stunted to let him.
好吧  我  我只是  试图  但是  现在我不得不说
Okay, uh, I'm--i'm-- I'm trying to be, uh... I am, but this right here?
这正是你的问题所在
This--this-- this is exactly your problem.
你太过于投入了
You get all wrapped up and involved and you
你甚至开始关心起这些人来了
Just-- you start--you start caring about these people.
你的病人在那里  他才是傻瓜
Your patient in there, he's the moron.
他的儿子从来没有满足过他的心愿
His son's never gonna give him what he wants,
他才是该失望的人
And he's just gonna be disappointed.
他一失望  你居然也感到
And the sooner he gets that, the sooner you get it...
不要停  说下去啊
No, go on, please.
你这个自私鬼
Be a selfish ass.
我至少知道应该期待些什么
'cause at least then I know what to expect.
你一会儿人模人样  一会儿又是不折不扣的混蛋
'cause this being a decent guy one second and a total jerk the next,
你这招太老了  阿历克斯
It's getting really old, alex.
所以你到底想怎么样  选一个吧
So who's it gonna be? pick one.
-欧麦利  -忙什么老兄?
-O'malley.  -'sup, bud?
你今天没来吃午饭
Hey. missed you at lunch today.
这真是一个升级版的地狱
It was an all-new level of hell.
不是的  我是在忙着填表格
Oh, no, I was busy doing my own charts.
-那些实习生都不尊重我  -如果我是我会的
-The interns don't respect me. -I would respect you if I was your intern.
乔治  他们不尊重你是因为他们不怕你
George, they don't respect you because they're not scared of you.
每隔几天就挑一个羞辱一下
Just decimate one every few days.
多简单的事儿啊  2号
It's not rocket science. two.
赫曼女士的肾要捐给谁
Who's getting, uh, ms. herman's kidney?
我  我可以查查
Uh, I can-- I can go check.
-3号  -瓦林先生
-Three?  -mr. walling.
没错  我全忘了
That's right. no. I totally forgot.
你忘了
You forgot.
像是你巡房前忘记做笔记?
Like you forgot to do your notes before rounds?
还是像是在做小肠梗阻的时候忘记钻洞?
Or like you forgot to pull the drain on my post-op s.b.o.?
或者像是忘记做笔录  导致你所有的病例  不
Or like you forgot to sign all your dictation, so all your charts-- uh,
我的病例全部作废?
My charts--are delinquent?
你忘记了
You forgot...
是因为你那颗才豆子那么大的脑袋里
Because the only thing you can retain in that
唯一能记住的就是什么时候吃午饭
Pea-sized brain of yours is what time lunch is.
格蕾将来会成为一个外科医生
Grey here is gonna become a surgeon
而你将来就只能在路边挖水沟
While you dig ditches by the side of the road.
很残忍  但是有效
It's brutal, but it's effective.
我不会和你这样下去
I am not gonna do this with you.
-怎样下去  -冷战
-Do what?  -have this silent fight.
我要给编辑写信
I'm gonna write the editors and have them
让他们更正  是谢博德-格蕾方法
Print a correction-- the shepherd-grey method.
我不希望你承认我是因为觉得我抓狂了
I don't want you to give me credit because you're mad that I'm mad.
我希望你承认我的能力
I want you to give me credit because you
是因为觉得我很努力  值得承认
Think I worked hard for it and I deserve it.
你不值得承认  你还只是个孩子
You don't deserve it. you're a baby.
你有潜力成为好的外科医生  甚至是伟大的
You have the potential to be a good surgeon, maybe a great one.
但是你还没有弄清楚自己该学的是什么
But you haven't even scratched the surface on what you need to learn.
那是我的主意
It was my idea.
我讨厌那张照片
And I hate that picture.
急诊室需要注射注射护士
Any available i.v. nurse to the e.r.
器官共享联合网络没有合适的供体
U.n.o.s. doesn't have a match.
好吧
Okay.
我们可以...
Uh, we can, um...
我们已经暂停手术  病人们都还在
We've been stalling. we haven't released anyone.
我可以和莫休夫人谈谈
I can talk to ms.Mercer
你什么都不能做  会被看作是强迫的
you can't do anything that could be seen as coercion.
器官共享网络那里已经讲的很明白了
U.n.o.s. is very clear.
但是
But,Sir
我们不得不失去器官移植中心的地位了
the last thing we need is to lose our status as a transplant center.
让病人们回家吧
Let the patients go home.
都结束了
It's over.
一小时后我要做个手术  一起喝杯咖啡?
I've got a cabg in an hour. want to get some coffee?
这样我很不适应
I'm not cut out for this.
咖啡?
Coffee?
不  是我不适应触摸以及...和女性做爱
No, this, the--the touching and the... sex with a girl.
我做不来  我本来以为我可以的
I just--i-i can't do it. I thought I could but...
但你昨天可以啊  我不明白
But you did do it. I don't understand.
你感觉不好
It wasn't good for you.
真不能相信
I can't believe it.
我已经那么接近
I got so close.
你在等待器官名单上排名很高的
You're gonna be pretty high on the transplant list.
一定会有适合的出现的
Something else will come up.
我并不是为了移植的事情难过
It's not the kidney I'm upset about.
你的儿子
Oh. your son.
我们一年没有说过话了
We hadn't spoken in over a year.
我花了好几个月才找到他
It took me months to find him.
这是我和他和好的好机会
This was my chance to get him back.
没错
Right.
我知道P.J.有点自私
I know p.j. can be selfish...
粗鲁
Rude...
他也很不容易
But it hasn't been easy for him.
她的妈妈死了
His mom died.
我每天工作到很晚
I worked late most nights.
我做错了很多事
I made a lot of mistakes.
你不能责怪你自己
You can't blame yourself.
哀莫大于心死
Some people are just broken.
我觉得你可以试着不要那么期待
I guess you just try not to care too much.
这样就不会失望
Then you can't be disappointed.
这是你的出院文件
These are, uh, your discharge papers.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我不知道为什么会这样
I don't know why I'm...
对不起
I'm sorry.
太抱歉了
I'm so sorry.
没关系
It's okay.
在底下签名  你就可以离开了
Now all you have to do is sign there at the bottom, and you're free to go.
你肯定觉得我是个坏人
You must think I'm a terrible person...
拒绝捐肾
Refusing to give my kidney.
我们没有这么觉得  夫人
We're not thinking anything, ma'am.
他拿走了我的一切
He's taken everything.
我的爱  我的骄傲  我的自尊  都拿走了
My love, my pride, my dignity-- it's all gone.
只有我的肾他还没有拿走
But the one thing that he doesn't have is the kidney.
我不能想象把自己最后仅有的也给他
And the thought of giving him that last part of me...
你肯定觉得我是个坏人
You must think I'm a terrible person.
我有一个规定
I'm not allowed to think anything.
不能给病人任何倾向性的意见
There are rules that prevent me from having an opinion here good rules
存在规则的原因是  捐器官给别人
Rules in place for a reason-- because giving an organ that god put in
是绝对不能被强迫的
Your body to someone else isn't something that you can be coerced into doing.
那是  一件大事
It is... a big thing.
是一件不平凡的事
It is an extraordinary thing.
那必须是心甘情愿给予的礼物
It's a gift that must be freely given.
如果你愿意捐献  当然我没有在劝你必须捐
And if you were to give it, and I'm not asking you to,
但是如果你愿意捐献  这不仅仅将救活你的丈夫
But if you were to give it, it's not just for your husband.
你将救活5个人  5个素不相识的人
It's for five other people, people that you don't know from adam.
六个捐赠者已经麻醉好可以进手术室了
Our six donors are all anesthetized and ready to go.
先给他们手术  再给受赠者手术
They'll be done first, followed by the recipients.
每一对将被用颜色编码防治弄混
Each pair will be color-coded so as not to confuse them.
手术很复杂 大家要动作快而且仔细
This surgery is a hornet's nest, people, so work quickly but carefully.
彼此认真合作
Use each other. operate as a team.
让我们来创造医学历史吧
Let's go make medical history.
那个女人能改变主意我们真是太幸运了
We're lucky as hell that woman changed her mind.
是的  我们太幸运了
Yes, we are. yes, we are.
这就是我常说的漂亮的健康肾
Huh. now that's what I call a nice-looking kidney.
放到冰上开始用保存液冲洗
Put that on ice and start flushing in the preservation solution.
你想试试吗  杨医生
You want to do the honors, dr. yang?
很好
Good.
来吧
come on.
尿如泉涌啊  主任
That's quite a geyser of urine, sir.
这意味着我们做的很好
That means we did our job right.
你永远不会讨厌看到它
You never get tired of seeing that.
我们好了  格蕾
We're ready for you, grey.
我要捧着肾过来了
Walking with the kidney.
黄金5秒钟  黄金5秒钟
five second rule.five second rule
拿稳了  伯奇
hold it still, boki.
我需要更多的冰还有绳子
I'm gonna need more ice, uh, and another tie.
我去拿
I'll get it.
不  你什么都不准碰
No, you don't touch anything else.
有人居然把把肾弄掉了?
Someone dropped a damn kidney?
我知道你不想和我谈这个
I know you don't want to talk about it anymore.
-我知道你讨厌这个  -看在上帝的份上
-I know you're over it. -oh, for the love of god.
听我说完
Just hear me out.
我喜欢自己游刃有余
I like to be good at things, okay?
我不失败
I do not fail.
我不退出
I do not quit.
我喜欢擅长一些事  我想要擅长做爱
I like to be good at things, and I want to be good at this.
所以  我需要你
So... I need you.
我需要你教我
I need you to show me.
教你?
Show you?
虽然你没有发明什么临床试验
Just because you didn't publish a big Clinical trial
不能否认你仍然是个天才
doesn't mean you're not a genius.
好  脱掉你的裤子
Fine. take off your pants.
真的吗  天啊  谢谢你
Really? oh, my god. thank you.
太谢谢你了
Thank you so much.
我来教你斯隆的方法
I'll show you the sloan method.
这本应在医学杂志上出版的
Won't ever be in a medical journal, but it should.
现在不是应该变成粉红色了吗
Shouldn't it be pinking up by now?
它现在只有静脉血
It's just getting venous blood.
让我们在检查下背面
Let's check the back side again.
我想我看到了...也许一点粉色
I think I see... a little pink, maybe.
快点  快点
Ah, come on, come on.
好吧
All right.
来吧
Come on.
来吧  变粉
Come on, pink up.
来吧
Come on.
变粉  变粉  变粉  变粉
Pink up, pink up, pink up, pink up.
来吧
Come on.
太好了  看起来不错
Yes. yeah, it looks good.
肾移植成功
We have a live kidney.
来吧  我可以给2个实习医生给你
Oh, come on. I am offering two interns.
买一送一  来吧
Two interns for the price of one--come on.
我用罗拉来换他们两个
I'll trade you Laura for both of 'em.
李欧很会挤脓  而且还很喜欢
Leo drains pus and likes it.
我把一个器官掉地上了
I dropped an internal organ...on the floor.
这时有发生
It happens.
好了  好了  这个怎么样
Okay, okay. Uh, how about this?
4号跟乔治  我要詹姆斯
Four goes to George. I get James.
克莱夫  给你2号  伊兹让出李欧
Karev, you get two. Izzie, give Leo.
你们在干什么
What are you people doing?
我们只是在商量
We were just, uh, just deciding which
把哪个实习医生分给乔治
of our interns to give to George.
你们认为我当初有选择权
Oh, you think I got to choose my interns,
而且我选你们做我的实习生
and I picked you people 'cause
是因为你们是外科的梦之队吗
you're all such a surgical dream team?
你  你懒惰  你脾气暴躁
You--you're lazy. You're whiny.
那笨手笨脚的人
Butterfingers over there
看起来很压抑  还有你  杨
is downright depressing, and you, Yang,
你  你真让人讨厌
You-- you're just annoying.
自己选自己的实习医生
Choosing their own interns...
那个什么  什么
What are--what...
把那些该死的卡片给我
Give me those damn cards.
欧麦利
O'malley...
你有实习医生
You have interns.
那是什么
What is it?
好的  打开他的输液口
Okay, open his fluids.
克莱夫  给他注射一克的球蛋白
Karev, push a gram of mag.
做一个全血细胞分析和电解质
do a c.b.c. and electrolytes.
斯蒂文斯  帮他去做一个彩色多普勒超声
Stevens, uh, order a color flow doppler
和一个全身的神经检查
and do a full neuro workup.
你认为有内出血
You think there's a bleed?
我们只有在检查完
There's no way of knowing till
才会知道
we evaluate everything.
pj到哪里去了
where is... P.J.?
我儿子去哪里了
Where's my son?
斯坦死了没
Stan had better be dead right now.
他会很好的
He's doing fine.
他没有打过电话给我
He hasn't called my room.
躺下
Just lay back.
他没有问候过我
He hasn't asked for me.
这都过了3年了
It's been three years.
我给了一个肾给他
I gave a kidney for him,
但他还是没有做出选择
and he still hasn't made a choice.
他没有打电话给你和问候你
He hasn't asked about you or called.
我想他已经做决定了
I think he's made a choice.
但是我给了一个肾给他
But I gave a kidney for him.
我给了一个肾
I gave a kidney.
天啊
Oh, my god.
老兄  一个小时前护士
Hey, man, the nurse was supposed to
就应该给我送饭了吧
to bring my dinner like an hour ago.
你爸爸突然发病了
Your dad just had a seizure.
那是什么意思
Okay. So what does that mean?
就是意外发生了
It means something's wrong.
也就是说他可能会死
It means he could be dying,
他不知道你在捣乱
and he doesn't know you give a crap.
老实说  他不知道
Honestly, he doesn't know, and maybe
可能你没有  但是如果你在捣乱  他会死的
you don't, but if you do, he's dying,
到时就太迟了  阿历克斯  别这样
And you're gonna be too late. Alex, stop.
他在呼叫你  但是你来得也太晚了吧
He's asking for you, and you're gonna be too late,
你想这样胡乱捣蛋地
And you're gonna live with it
过你的下半生吗
for the rest of your life!
你真的想这样过吗  你想吗
You really want to live with that,huh? Do you?
阿历克斯  阿历克斯
Alex! Alex.
那我们明天见
So tomorrow we'll meet,
提前一个小时到
one hour before pre-rounds.
老兄  那是  凌晨4点
Dude, that's, like, 4:00 a.m.
斯蒂文斯医生从没
Dr. stevens never made us
要求我们提前一个小时到
come in before pre-rounds.
是的  欧麦利  你真冷血
Yeah, O'malley, you gotta chill.
他们应该叫欧麦利医生
They probably should say Dr. O'malley.
所以那些是你的实习医生
So those are your interns?
你怎么没有要求我当你的实习生啊
Did you even ask for me?
什么
What?
我曾帮你温习
I helped you study.
我还帮你粉刷你那烂抽屉
I helped decorate your stupid locker.
我  你没有  你没有
I--and you didn't-- you don't
你都不会留意这些
you don't even see it.
你什么都没留意
You don't see anything.
我真是个白痴
I am such an idiot.
而你是个混蛋
And you are a jerk.
你从来都未想过要我吗
You didn't even think to ask for me?
你去死吧  欧麦利医生
Screw you, Dr. O'malley.
卡拉斯先生  帕特先生
Uh, Mr. Cross, Mr. Patel,
陈小姐  罗宁小姐和莫休先生
Ms.Chen, Ms. Loring and Mr.mercer
他们都稳定了
they're all stable.
但是瓦林先生  他推迟了一直的日期
But Mr. Walling, he has delayed graft function
和其他乱七八糟的东西
and god knows what else.
这些全都推到明天
Ah, the press is gonna be all over this tomorrow.
我希望你帮我去面试
And I'll need you available for interviews
和筛选照片
and some photo-ops.
你一定要穿上你最得体的衣服
Make sure you wear your nice scrubs.
你听到没有 先生
Did you hear me, sir?
瓦林先生  他的情况异常复杂
Mr.Walling--he has a serious complication.
电解质混乱  生命体征不稳
His electrolytes are off, his crit's down.
但是你保住了其他5个人的生命
But you saved five other lives.
这已经是一个非常好的成绩了
That's a pretty good scorecard.
不是最好  但是很好
Not perfect, but good.
我告诉过你  我不想看到斯坦
I told you. I don't want to see Stan.
我不是带你去看斯坦
I'm not taking you to see Stan.
就是她
Oh, this is her.
这个女人捐了一个肾给我
This is the woman who gave me her kidney.
她怎么样了
How's she doing?
我一直都很留意她
I'm keeping a close eye on her,
到目前为止  她恢复良好
but so far, she's completely stable.
跟我来
Come with me.
这个男人病得很重  可能快死了
This man is very ill, maybe dying.
他得到了捐赠者一个很好很健康的肾
He's got a perfect, healthy donor kidney
而且那个肾没有掉地上
that wasn't dropped on the floor.
我们能帮的只有这些
There's only so much we can help...
我们伤害的也只有这些
And so much we can hurt.
不要再自责了
Forgive yourself.
探病时间过了
Visiting hours are over.
没关系的
It's okay.
你的排尿量生到每小时25cc
Your urine output is up to 25 cc's per hour.
你应该很开心的
That should make you happy.
我妻子应该会很开心的
My wife would've been happy.
谁还会在意我的排尿量是多少
Who's gonna care about my urine output now?
事情会有转机的
Well, things are gonna be a little different.
贝利医生
Ah, Dr. Bailey.
我听说你今天做的大手术非常成功
I heard your big surgery went well today.
恭喜恭喜
Congratulations.
彼此彼此拉
Same to you.
看到你的名字写在上面
Must feel good to see
感觉一定很好吧
your name in print like that.
你知道  如果梅瑞狄斯
It would feel better if
不是这样的话会更高兴
meredith wasn't so-- you know,
她在论文方面像个呆子
She's acting silly about the credit.
她变得很情绪化
She's getting emotional.
一个女生跟你在一起
That girl worked her ass off for you,
你还说她没有对文章作出贡献
and you got all the credit.
我对我们之间的失败负全责
I would've gotten all the blame had we failed.
但你没有失败啊
But you didn't fail.
这很简单  我对她来说相当于
It's simple. I'm an attending.
第二年的住院医生
She's a second-year resident.
你现在跟谁住在一起啊
Who you're now living with.
那不是简单  是混乱
That's not simple. It's messy.
如果是我  我会谢绝
If it were me, I'd start with "thank you."
看看你们会走多远
You'd be surprised how far that one goes,
特别是和我们的情绪化呆子一起
especially with us silly, emotional women.
-德里克说我是个婴儿  -什么
- So Derek said that I was a baby. - What?
我还有很多东西要学习
And that I had a lot to learn.
但是
Whatever.
我的意思是  不管怎么说他都是对的
I mean, not whatever. He's right.
我把肾掉地上了
I did drop a kidney.
不要说时有发生  因为从未发生过
And don't say it happens, because it doesn't.
我真的很讨厌他正确的时候
But I do hate it when he's right.
不  好的  他不正确
No, okay, he is not right.
别这么在意他的看法
Stop caring so much about what he thinks.
这会让你看起来很绝望
It makes you seem desperate.
好的  为了那个把实习医生耍得团团转的人
Okay, to the one trolling for interns.
好了  我改变主意了
Yeah, I changed my mind.
实习医生是很弱的  我不要弱者
Interns are weak. I don't want weak.
你知道吗  伯克是个男人
You know, Burke was a man.
他是个男人
He was a man.
乔
Joe.
我觉得  我们还要一轮
I think, uh, we need another round.
你好  乔  最近怎么样了
Hey, Joe. How you doing?
不好意思  给你的
Excuse me. Here you go.
-给我的  -对
- Wh--ho-- is this for me? - Yes.
亲爱的  我给你买了玫瑰
Hey, honey. I brought you roses.
我们回家吧
Let me back in the house.
-不会吧  -太好了
- No.  - Yes.
天啊  那究竟是什么东西
Holy crap. What the hell is that thing?
那是一个装在罐子的肾
Oh, that is a kidney in a jar.
实在太不公平了
That's not fair.
你怎么得来的
How did you get that?
过程不重要
Well, being an incredibly important,
把它看成是神经科医生的津贴
fancy neurosurgeon has its perks.
谢谢
Thank you.
如果不是你我不会这样
I couldn't have done it without you,
没有手术  没有病人
Not one surgery, not one patient.
没有你我什么都做不成
I couldn't have done any of it without you.
谢谢
Thanks.
好的
Yeah,
你们要不继续喝酒  或者
Could you guys go ahead and get this thing the
把这个东西拿走吗
hell out of here before people
-抢在人们开始尖叫之前  -可以
start to freak out? Okay.
好的  你还好吗
Okay. Um, are you gonna be okay?
很好  很好 继续
Yeah, yeah, go ahead.
-好的  晚安  -晚安
- All right. Good night. - Good night.
晚安  乔
Good night, Joe.
选组真能体现生活的残酷
The thing about choosing teams in real life,
根本不像上体育课
It's nothing like it used to be in gym class.
第一个被选择的人很幸福
Being first pick can be terrifying.
脱掉你的裤子
Take off your pants.
什么
Excuse me?
脱掉  你的裤子
Take off... your pants.
我们再试一次
We're trying this again.
然后最后一个被选择的就
And being chosen last...
是世界上最倒霉的一件事
Isn't the worst thing in the world.
干嘛
What?
我喜欢你
I care about you.
我在乎你  我没有疯
I care about you, and I'm not gonna go crazy,
我不打算自杀
And I'm not gonna try to kill myself,
我不打算停止喜欢你
and I'm not gonna stop caring about you,
无论你把我推得多远
no matter how hard you push me away.
闭嘴  离开我的房间
Shut up and get out of my room.
不
No.
我喜欢你
I care about you.
我知道你也喜欢我
And I know you care about me, too.
我们现在开始也不迟
It is not too late for us.
离开我的房间
Get out of my room.
承认吧  承认你也喜欢我
Admit it. Admit that you care about me, too.
我知道你喜欢的  我也喜欢你
I know you do, and I care about you.
我喜欢你
I care about you.
我喜欢你  我喜欢你
I care about you. I care about you.
我们旁观者
I-- so we watch from the sidelines,
把隔阂粘在一起
clinging to our isolation...
它在生长
It glows.
对啊
Yeah.
我妈妈在当住院医生的时候
When my mother was a resident,
她没有把肾掉到地上
she wasn't dropping kidneys.
你在看你妈妈的日记
You're reading your mom's diary?
对
Yeah.
我及不上我妈妈一半
I'm not half the surgeon my mother was.
我们知道
Because we know as soon as
一旦我们离开
we let go of the bench...
什么  你要走了
What, are you leaving already?
这世上没有好男人  乔
There are no real men left in the world, Joe.
再见
See you.
Yeah.
来一杯啤酒  不  威士忌
Hey, shot and a beer. Uh, whiskey.
算了  我还是喝啤酒吧
You know what? Better make it just the beer.
我明天开始工作了
I start work tomorrow.
某人来了
Someone comes along and
游戏也会变得完全不一样了
changes the game completely.